[{"answer": "Not at all.", "docId": "121213pmt", "aSentId": 32, "question": "Were you surprised in the end that she fell on her sword today?", "qSentId": 31}, {"answer": "I didn't believe it because here you had an attack with rocket-propelled hand grenades, mortars, very well executed, very well prepared.", "docId": "121213pmt", "aSentId": 43, "question": "You didn't believe it?", "qSentId": 42}, {"answer": "ORGAN: Here's what she said.", "docId": "121213pmt", "aSentId": 55, "question": "Don't you -- don't you exercise some intelligence about this?", "qSentId": 54}, {"answer": "Common sense.", "docId": "121213pmt", "aSentId": 72, "question": "What was her job that day, Rudy, to be fair?", "qSentId": 71}, {"answer": "I don't know that.", "docId": "121213pmt", "aSentId": 81, "question": "But do you think she lied?", "qSentId": 80}, {"answer": "Also fair.", "docId": "121213pmt", "aSentId": 90, "question": "Is that a fair criticism?", "qSentId": 89}, {"answer": "Personally I don't believe she would serve the country well in that capacity.", "docId": "121213pmt", "aSentId": 111, "question": "Would you therefore object to her becoming secretary of state personally?", "qSentId": 110}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "121213pmt", "aSentId": 128, "question": "Would I support it?", "qSentId": 127}, {"answer": "I think our -- some people in our military are going to have a very hard time.", "docId": "121213pmt", "aSentId": 132, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 131}, {"answer": "Well, what I'm saying is I'm not President Obama.", "docId": "121213pmt", "aSentId": 136, "question": "If you were President Obama then, who would you go for?", "qSentId": 135}, {"answer": "I think so, because it seems so obvious that you have to do it.", "docId": "121213pmt", "aSentId": 146, "question": "Are you looking at this as a pre-Christmas done deal, Rudy?", "qSentId": 145}, {"answer": "I agree there should be a sensible debate about it.", "docId": "121213pmt", "aSentId": 189, "question": "What is your view?", "qSentId": 188}, {"answer": "Norway.", "docId": "121213pmt", "aSentId": 191, "question": "I didn't -- I didn't agree, I didn't agree that it necessarily should result in immediate gun control because I look at the murder that took place in Norway or in Finland where, what, 79 people were killed without a gun?", "qSentId": 190}, {"answer": "If he doesn't get the AR-15, he'll go get a handgun.", "docId": "121213pmt", "aSentId": 206, "question": "Why not?", "qSentId": 205}, {"answer": "There's no question about it.", "docId": "121213pmt", "aSentId": 214, "question": "-- running a country with so many guns to try and make it harder?", "qSentId": 213}, {"answer": "Let me start with you, Margaret Hoover.", "docId": "121213pmt", "aSentId": 249, "question": "How are you?", "qSentId": 248}, {"answer": "I don't know for them if it's as much personally about her or if it's about Benghazi.", "docId": "121213pmt", "aSentId": 253, "question": "Are they right to be pleased about this?", "qSentId": 252}, {"answer": "Yes -- no.", "docId": "121213pmt", "aSentId": 293, "question": "That's not great for a progressive president like Barack Obama, is it?", "qSentId": 292}, {"answer": "Well, first, I'm afraid you know more about me than I know, so that's my first concern.", "docId": "121213pmt", "aSentId": 391, "question": "What's it like to be Warren Buffett's son?", "qSentId": 390}, {"answer": "Three years.", "docId": "121213pmt", "aSentId": 404, "question": "How long was the period?", "qSentId": 403}, {"answer": "Oh, no, it was a deal.", "docId": "121213pmt", "aSentId": 413, "question": "I mean, did he ever even nearly succumb to the pressure?", "qSentId": 412}, {"answer": "Yes -- no, the handshake was it.", "docId": "121213pmt", "aSentId": 420, "question": "Was there a formal handshake, a contract?", "qSentId": 419}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "121213pmt", "aSentId": 422, "question": "That's it?", "qSentId": 421}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "121213pmt", "aSentId": 424, "question": "Has your dad always been a handshake man?", "qSentId": 423}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "121213pmt", "aSentId": 426, "question": "Are you all like that?", "qSentId": 425}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "121213pmt", "aSentId": 429, "question": "And you're all the same?", "qSentId": 428}, {"answer": "Well, I think the things that have worked -- I'm not sure exactly specifically what you're after.", "docId": "121213pmt", "aSentId": 444, "question": "What did work over the years?", "qSentId": 443}, {"answer": "I don't think you have to pay more tax.", "docId": "121213pmt", "aSentId": 489, "question": "Would you be happy to pay more tax?", "qSentId": 488}, {"answer": "Now you've put me on the spot.", "docId": "121213pmt", "aSentId": 499, "question": "Final question, what on Earth do you buy Warren Buffett for Christmas?", "qSentId": 498}, {"answer": "You go with any idea you have.", "docId": "121213pmt", "aSentId": 503, "question": "Do you go small?", "qSentId": 502}, {"answer": "Oh, my gosh.", "docId": "121213pmt", "aSentId": 505, "question": "What did you get him last year?", "qSentId": 504}, {"answer": "No, he loves it.", "docId": "121213pmt", "aSentId": 512, "question": "I bet he's never happier, right?", "qSentId": 511}, {"answer": "It was incredibly difficult.", "docId": "121213pmt", "aSentId": 549, "question": "How difficult has it been for you, Damien?", "qSentId": 548}, {"answer": "I've actually gained 60 pounds in the past year that I was out, because now I have adequate nutrition and decent exercise, things like that.", "docId": "121213pmt", "aSentId": 559, "question": "What else?", "qSentId": 558}, {"answer": "First of all, it's amazing to have him out here with us.", "docId": "121213pmt", "aSentId": 564, "question": "And how do you think he's been coping?", "qSentId": 563}, {"answer": "It's the little things, like going to the bank and filling out a deposit slip or going through security at the airport.", "docId": "121213pmt", "aSentId": 574, "question": "What do you think have been the hardest things for Damien to deal with?", "qSentId": 573}, {"answer": "Well, the story had so many twists and turns.", "docId": "121213pmt", "aSentId": 580, "question": "What was it that appealed to you from a documentary maker pointing of view?", "qSentId": 579}, {"answer": "And what you didn't hear was actually that that knife was actually thrown in the lake a year before the murders even happened.", "docId": "121213pmt", "aSentId": 594, "question": "Of course the lottery turned out to be a shameful farce, didn't it?", "qSentId": 593}, {"answer": "It's absolutely nightmarish.", "docId": "121213pmt", "aSentId": 634, "question": "When you hear that, given your knowledge and experience of Death Row, given what we now know about DNA and the way it's been exonerating many people on Death Row, what do you think of it?", "qSentId": 633}, {"answer": "I would say in the time I was there, probably three others.", "docId": "121213pmt", "aSentId": 642, "question": "How many people did you meet or encounter on Death Row who you basically believe may have been innocent?", "qSentId": 641}, {"answer": "CHOLS: I don't know, because they wanted to convict us so badly.", "docId": "121213pmt", "aSentId": 647, "question": "Would DNA evidence, had it been around when you were arrested, have cleared you from the start?", "qSentId": 646}, {"answer": "It's sort of -- really what it comes down to, it helps me deal.", "docId": "121213pmt", "aSentId": 654, "question": "What the significant of those?", "qSentId": 653}, {"answer": "These are runes.", "docId": "121213pmt", "aSentId": 659, "question": "What are the ones on your knuckles?", "qSentId": 658}, {"answer": "I could not have survived in prison or out of prison without her.", "docId": "121213pmt", "aSentId": 686, "question": "How important to you and powerful to you has it been to have Lorri's unequivocal backing and support through all of this?", "qSentId": 685}, {"answer": "He wanted to take me to the desert to see the wild flowers.", "docId": "121213pmt", "aSentId": 713, "question": "Where did you go?", "qSentId": 712}, {"answer": "Yeah, absolutely.", "docId": "121213pmt", "aSentId": 722, "question": "You turned down Marlon Brando?", "qSentId": 721}, {"answer": "It was fine.", "docId": "121213pmt", "aSentId": 724, "question": "How did he take rejection?", "qSentId": 723}]